[Gil-su] Hey, where's
that other punk? Huh?
- Is that little asshole bringing the cops?
- [Beom-seok panting]
[tense music playing]
You dumb little high school bitch.
I got ya.
- [boy 1 grunts]
- [Gil-su] Hey.
- Faster.
- [boy 1] It's heavy.
- [Gil-su] You got the paperwork?
- [boy 2] I brought everything.
- [Gil-su] Then hurry up.
- [tape rustling]
[sirens approaching]
Hey, hey, hey. Hurry up.
- [boy 2] Oh shit.
- [Gil-su] Hurry up!
[boy 3] Shit, shit! All right, hurry!
- Hurry up! Come on!
- [car door slides open]
[sirens continue]
- [boy 3] Come on, come on, come on!
- [boy 2] Let's get outta here!
[sirens continue]
[ringing tone]
KIM GIL-SU
- Hey, hyeong. Sorry, my battery was dead.
- Don't fucking bullshit me.
Tell me where you are!
[spluttering] Hey, it's over.
So you better come to Mangu-dong
with Yeong-i, that fucking bitch.
[Gil-su breathing heavily]
Seong-chan is here.
You better fucking hurry.
Or else I'm gonna
sell him somewhere. Got it?
Yes.
[phone beeps]
Seong-chan? What'd he say?
[Seok-dae] I need to get going.
You stay here.
Rent out a room for a few days.
[Yeong-i] Where are you going?
[Seok-dae] Don't follow me.
Oppa!
- [sighs]
- [phone buzzing]
ASSHOLE
[tense music continues]
What happened? What's going on?
I'm at the address you gave me,
but no one's here.
[breathing shakily]
And those shitheads took Su-ho,
didn't they?
Send me a friend request on WithMap,
like right now.
What?
[Yeong-i] You don't have it?
WithMap's on the app store. Download it.
It's a location-sharing app,
so get it and follow me.
[grunts softly]
- Where are you going?
- [Yeong-i] I don't know yet.
Make sure you bring the police.
Or we're really gonna die.
Okay.
[phone beeps]
Oppa!
I'm not letting you go alone.
I'm coming with you.
[tense music continues]
[Su-ho] It's all right, 'kay?
- Bye.
- [Beom-seok] Why's Su-ho going alone?
What are we gonna do?
What if something happens?
[phone buzzes]
YEONG-I:
COME TO MANGU-DONG FIRST
YOUR FRIENDS ARE THERE
[music fades]
["Hero" by Meego playing]
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 1
[birdsong]
[ominous music playing]
[Seok-dae sighs]
You're so annoying.
How long are you gonna follow me?
[Yeong-i] Hey, knock it off.
[Su-ho inhales]
[exhales]
[Beom-seok] Su-ho-ya.
[Su-ho exhales]
[grunts]
- [sighs]
- You all right?
Hey, how'd you, uh…
how'd you end up here?
- I thought that you might be in trouble.
- Oh.
I was kinda worried.
I went to that guy's house
to give him the money,
but then they took me here.
Oh.
[chuckles]
Hey, that warms me up
like doganitang. Wow.
- Hey, hey.
- [Su-ho] I could go for a drink.
Hey, assholes.
Shut your fucking mouths, all right?
Hey, let us talk over here.
I'm sad enough as it is,
being tied up like this.
- Smoking's really bad for your health.
- You keep talking.
Oh shit.
[Yeong-i sighs]
ASSHOLE
- [bleeping]
- [Seok-dae] Yeong-a.
Yeah?
Remember to stay quiet.
Don't act up.
[sighs]
You always say the same thing.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault we got involved
with Gil-su to begin with.
This wouldn't have happened
if you hadn't followed me.
Hey.
Do you like me?
Don't be an idiot.
- [bleep]
- [ringing tone]
[Si-eun] Hello?
I just made a report about Mangu-dong.
Are you on your way?
[ominous music continues]
[sighs]
Come here.
Hey, Seok-dae-ya.
Did I… do something to hurt your feelings?
I fed you and housed you.
I mean, I even paid you a lot of money.
Why?
Did your heart get soft because
you got a family of your own?
I'll take the beating, hyeong.
[Gil-su] Mm-mm-mm.
I was just curious.
Get it over with.
All right.
Take the beating then, asshole.
[grunting]
[metal clanks]
You piece of shit. Huh?
Fuck. You shithead motherfucker!
[grunts]
Oppa!
[Gil-su panting]
Oppa, please don't.
Bitch! So you… you did it.
You're responsible for this.
Hey, take this bitch and get rid of her.
- [bar clangs]
- Get off!
- [blow lands]
- [Yeong-i] Let go, you fucking assholes!
- [bar clatters]
- [Yeong-i] Let go of me!
- Get your grubby hands off me!
- [grunting]
[Gil-su exhales]
Hey, Seong-chan-a.
Hey, Seong-chan-a!
[sighs]
[ominous music continues]
You're turning 14 this year, right?
Yes.
[Gil-su chuckles]
So you stab those guys then, all right?
- Don't be such a coward.
- [breathing shakily]
[Gil-su] You're a minor.
You won't get thrown in jail.
Ugh, I'm anxious.
JUNGNANG-GU
YEONG-I
[bleeping]
[exhales]
[Gil-su singing]
♪ Which one of you should I stab? ♪
Eenie, meenie,
minie,
moe.
Ding, dong, ding… dong.
[all laughing]
Hey, man.
Let's work something out.
Shut your mouth.
Yeah? This might sting a little.
Okay?
[groaning]
Enough is enough, goddamn piece of shit.
- [Su-ho] Whoa.
- [Gil-su grunting]
[panting]
[coughs]
[Yeong-i] Oppa!
- Everybody stay still, or I will kill you.
- [Gil-su groans]
[Gil-su panting]
Let's go, one on one, you and me.
- [Gil-su chuckles] Fucking shit.
- If I win, you leave us alone.
What, you take me for a punk-ass bitch?
You asshole. Fuck you.
Fuckin' bitch.
Hey! Let go of me, you fucking shithead!
Ha! Come here. Fuck.
Goddamn asshole!
- I gave you food and a place to stay!
- Fucker!
- Right?
- [Seok-dae grunts]
[Gil-su groans]
Damn it.
Stop before you really
get your ass beat to hell.
[laughs] Goddamn!
Ha! Aah.
[Seok-dae grunts]
[Gil-su laughs] Hey, Seok-dae-ya.
Are you at least havin' fun? Huh?
- You know that you'll never beat me.
- [groans]
Because your big dumbass
heart gets in the way.
- You piece of--
- [grunts]
[Gil-su groans]
Fuck.
- You dumb bitch.
- You hit him from behind?
Enough is enough, you goddamn fuckers!
- You fucking bitch, I'll--
- You wanna fuck around and find out?
[boy 1 chuckles]
Oh!
Get Seok-dae oppa.
- [Gil-su groans]
- [Yeong-i] Hey, don't move.
- [boy 2] Fucking bitch.
- Hey, stay where you are, asshole!
[Gil-su moaning]
- Oh my God.
- [Gil-su] Agh, one sec. Hold on.
- Agh. I'm bleeding.
- [panting]
Just a minute.
- [Yeong-i yelps]
- [Gil-su] Goddamn bitch.
- [Gil-su] You fucking bitch.
- [knife clatters]
- Die, you little shit.
- [yelps]
[grunts]
Ever since Seok-dae fucking met you…
Die.
[Yeong-i] Shit. Stop it.
- Hold up.
- [boy 2] Hyeong! Hyeong!
- [Gil-su grunts]
- [siren blaring in distance]
[Yeong-i coughing and gasping]
[whimpering]
[coughing]
- [Si-eun sighs]
- [Gil-su scoffs] Fuck.
I thought you were a dumbass kid.
But you're freakin' brave, aren't you?
It's over. The police are here.
They'll probably search
your car down there.
Goddamn it.
- [boy 3] Shit.
- [boy 2] Let's go.
[wheezing]
[coughing] Are you okay?
[siren continues in distance]
Si-eun-a, what's going on?
[Si-eun] I'm sorry I'm late.
- [Su-ho] We almost died. Can you untie us?
- Yeah.
[groans] Ow, my arms.
- [Si-eun] Let's get outta here.
- [laughs]
[sighs] Nice.
[groans] I'm never coming back
to an amusement park.
- [siren getting louder]
- [chuckles]
[sighs]
Hey, why are they back?
[Gil-su] For fuck's sake.
Hey.
- [siren sound effect continues]
- You think that you're so smart, don't ya?
These little fucking kids,
trying to trick me?
Fuck.
I'm done playing your game. Go get them!
Aw, man, you should've told us.
[dramatic music playing]
[boy 2] Kick their ass!
[grunting]
[both grunting]
[yells]
[grunting]
Here we go.
Yeong-a. Let's go.
We have to go.
[all panting]
Huh? The police.
- [officer 1] What?
- [Yeong-i] What are you doing?
- [Seok-dae] You gotta leave.
- [officer 1] Kids!
[boy 1 grunts] Come here!
- You psycho son of a bitch.
- [boy 3] You stupid fuckin' asshole.
- [Gil-su] Move aside.
- [boy 2] Fuck.
- [Si-eun gasps]
- [blade rings]
[Gil-su laughs]
Did you think I wouldn't stab you
just because you were a kid? Huh?
That's why you should've given me
the money when I asked for it,
you little shit.
Yeah? Huh?
- [gunshot]
- [gasps]
[officer 1] Don't move!
Hands up!
- [boy 1 coughs]
- [radio bleeps]
[officer 1] Number 220, this is 43.
- Suspects in report 2917 in an assault…
- You fucking little prick.
- Next time, you're dead.
- [officer 1] This is 43.
- [radio] Stay where you are.
- All suspects in… Don't move!
I think there's some kind
of misunderstanding.
- These are live bullets.
- [radio chatter]
Oh, we're cooperating, sir.
- Right?
- [boy 3] Uh-huh.
Wait, didn't we play soccer
together last month…
[boy 2 yelps]
- [grunting and panting]
- [officer 1] Nobody move.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- I'm not.
- [boy 3 yelps]
- [officer 1] Stay still.
Hey. Hey!
Yeon Si-eun!
- Where are you going?
- [boy 3 groans]
[dramatic music playing]
[panting]
[music fades]
[Gil-su gasps] You scared me.
Oh, fuck, this is
some fucking bullshit, man.
I hate this.
Hey, why you fuckin' following
me around? Huh?
[panting]
[menacing music playing]
[Gil-su] Jeez, this stupid little kid.
You're fuckin' impossible,
you little prick.
Ha!
[Si-eun coughs]
[Gil-su laughs]
[sighs] Where should I stab you?
Huh?
[Su-ho] Hey!
[Si-eun coughs]
Ah.
Guess I gotta kick your ass. [sighs]
Why have you both been coming
after me all day?
Shit, man, I'm so sick of this crap.
Well?
Come on.
[dramatic music playing]
[Gil-su grunts and laughs]
- You're pretty good, kid.
- [Su-ho] Yeah, and you're slow.
[Gil-su] Shit! Hey!
Hey!
[both grunting]
[Su-ho grunts]
That's it?
[Gil-su yells]
- Oh, man.
- [Su-ho] Yah!
[blows landing]
[both grunting]
[Gil-su laughs]
- [groans]
- [Su-ho] Eat shit.
[music stops]
[Su-ho and Si-eun panting]
Hey, have you lost your mind or what?
Why would you go by yourself, huh?
- You came.
- [Su-ho sighs]
[chuckles]
Wow, what a load of shit.
You know, you really are a psycho.
Yeah?
I'm not the only one.
[Su-ho] Aah.
You won't let me have the last word,
will you?
If I were you,
I'd let me win.
You psycho.
[laughs]
[both panting]
[siren wailing in distance]
[buckle clinking]
[Yeong-i panting]
- [gasps] Come here.
- [Seok-dae] Goddamn it.
[siren approaching]
What are you doing?
Stop messing around!
- [panting]
- [Seok-dae] Go.
- You must go.
- Stop this bullshit.
- Come with us!
- Fucking listen to me, Yeong-a!
- [whimpers]
- [Seok-dae] Go.
It's not your fault.
[gasps] You're really…
- [Seong-chan] Let's go, noona.
- Uh… hey! [weeping]
- [Seong-chan] Come on!
- Hey! Fuck this! Hey!
You're so annoying! Hey! Jeon Seok-dae!
- I can't believe you!
- [officer 2] Young man.
Put your hands up.
- I said hands up.
- [sirens growing louder]
[boy 1] Let me fucking go!
- I told you everything!
- [boy 2] Let go!
- Let me go!
- Shut up and cooperate.
Get your hands off me! I'm cooperating!
- [Gil-su] How humiliating. Shit.
- [officer 1] Come on!
- [sighs]
- [radio chatter]
- [officer 2] Stop resisting.
- [Gil-su] I'm not!
[siren blaring]
[Gil-su] I'm coming for ya
when I'm out, 'kay?
Yeah?
Damn it! Fuck!
- What's goin' on?
- [Gil-su groans]
Let's not cross paths anymore,
you fucking dick.
[Gil-su] Shit.
[groans]
Aah, doganitang.
Ah, I'm so hungry, seriously.
Doganitang. Aah.
Do you have a tapeworm or something?
The moment I thought about doganitang,
I just couldn't get it out of my mind.
- With kkakdugi. Oh, man.
- [Beom-seok] Here you guys are.
What? What a relief! You're still alive.
I thought this guy was dead.
Well, after you two left, I went
looking for Si-eun's phone and stuff,
but I couldn't see anything,
so I took a while.
- [rustling]
- Here.
The screen's a little broken. [chuckles]
Thanks.
[man] Uh, Yeon Si-eun-gun?
We need you to come
to the station to make a statement.
Your friend too.
SEOUL SEOCHO POLICE STATION
- [clamoring]
- [boy] You have no right to arrest me!
- [officer 1] Calm the hell down.
- [officer 2] Sit down.
I'm sorry.
- What?
- You were right.
Because of me, Su-ho…
Sorry.
Don't say that.
You were late
because I took the taxi alone.
I'm sorry too.
[footsteps approaching in corridor]
[sighs]
The superintendent and I made a deal.
It will be… our little secret.
You both are
completely irrelevant to this case.
What?
Si-eun-gun, your family doesn't need
to be made aware of this.
You should go home.
Excuse me.
The only person who did anything wrong
was the man named Kim Gil-su.
He blackmailed and exploited everybody.
I'd appreciate it
if you showed them mercy.
Okay. Go on home.
[sighs]
Did you keep it a secret from my father?
No.
We should head out too.
I mean…
[sighs] I asked you
to keep it a secret from him.
Let's go.
[shudders]
- [officer] Is that so?
- [murmur of voices]
- [boy] I'm telling you.
- I heard you.
- [boy] You have to understand.
- [officer] That's why I'm listening.
Hey, psycho.
Let's grab a bite to eat sometime.
Why do you all love food so much?
[siren wailing in distance]
[insects chirping]
- [Si-eun] What's up?
- [sighs]
How's Seok-dae oppa?
He's being questioned inside.
He'll be fine.
What about the others?
I can't reach anyone.
The youngest one went home.
And you?
[Gil-su] Hey. What the hell?
Huh?
The assemblyman wanted you
to give that man an eye for an eye.
- Sorry?
- [Gil-su laughs]
This is the police station.
- You're beating someone here?
- Go ahead.
Uh… I'm all right.
[laughs]
Bullshit fuckin' idiots. Fuck this.
[yells]
[groans]
- [man] Hey.
- [Gil-su groaning]
[tense music playing]
Stay still. Don't move a muscle.
- [Gil-su sighs]
- Now, watch what I do.
[Gil-su groans]
One, two. Okay? One, two.
[yelps]
- [thump]
- [Gil-su moans]
That… hurts… [moans]
- [man sighs]
- [Gil-su groans]
Use your imagination,
like you're hitting a punching bag.
[Gil-su laughs weakly] Okay. Hit me.
Dumb fuck. Hey, Maltese.
Come at me like your friends did. [sighs]
- Wait, never mind. [laughs]
- [thump]
[Gil-su] You're just their minion.
You're not their friend.
You're some kind of little fucking coward
compared to those guys.
All right, you fuckin' asshole.
Hey, hit me.
Do it!
Come on, hit me! Do it!
[music intensifying]
[music fades]
[clattering]
[door slides open]
[footsteps approaching]
[Su-ho sighs]
Hmm?
[Si-eun] Well,
she wanted to apologize.
Hello!
Wait. You don't seem like someone
who's here to apologize.
My bad.
[chuckles]
You're nuts. [groans]
How did it go with you?
I don't know if it's a good thing,
but Beom-seok's family's covering it up.
They took our names out of the case.
And Kim Gil-su's detained.
[sighs] Is Beom-seok's dad
a chairman of some place?
His family's secretary or whoever came by
and said they'd pay
my whole hospital bill.
I declined,
but should I have just accepted it?
[laughs]
He's an assemblyman. Oh Jin-won.
Wow.
[winces]
[sighs]
How long will you be in here?
I'll be discharged tomorrow.
It's a light fracture.
Then, like, can I sleep here tonight?
- [Su-ho] Yeah, do what you want.
- All right!
[quirky music playing]
Hey, you were freaking cool back there.
- Yeah, I'm pretty cool.
- Yeah, I got goosebumps.
[high-pitched] "You wanna fuck around
and find out?"
- [both chuckle]
- "Enough's enough, you goddamn fuckers!"
[laughs]
Why are you copying me, idiot?
Did you fall in love?
Enough's enough.
Too bad, so sad. I'm Si-eun's.
Are you two dating?
That's not happening.
That's not happening?
We know where each other's at
at all times.
That's just that app's main function.
You should just date each other.
You'd make a cute couple.
- Enough's enough.
- [Yeong-i giggles]
Ah! You little shit.
[music fades]
- [door opens]
- [lock bleeps]
- [door closes]
- [lock turns]
- [alarm bleeps]
[sighs]
[clock ticking]
- [footsteps approaching]
- [rustling]
Huh? What?
[both] What's this?
You were craving it.
Ugh, I'll gain weight eating this late.
Huh? Wow, look at how late it is.
You are so inconsiderate.
I guess I should eat some just to be nice.
Wow, it looks amazing! [giggling]
What is this feeling?
I just got the chills.
What's with you?
- What do you mean?
- I mean you.
You're being way too sweet.
Huh? Your eyes.
The way you act, talk.
And your face.
It's making me cringe.
[chuckles]
["Self" by Meego playing]
Huh? Huh?
Eat your food.
[Su-ho slurps]
[sighs deeply]
[Yeong-i] Si-eun,
you need to eat something too.
[Su-ho groans happily]
Are you a mind reader?
[slurps]
[music fades]
Well, before I'm an assemblyman,
I'm also a citizen and a father
and am naturally extremely interested
in the youth policies, obviously.
- [papers rustling]
- [soft gasping]
[muffled sobbing]
What?
[sighs]
[exhales]
Why did I ever bring you here?
[sighs] You are…
just the wrong kind of breed.
[sighs] You know that?
[melancholy music playing]
[sobbing]
[blow lands]
[Beom-seok sobs]
["Hero" by Meego playing]
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ You are my hero ♪
♪ My little hero ♪
♪ My little hero… ♪
[lyrics in Korean]
♪ You are my hero ♪
♪ My little hero… ♪
ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND EVENTS
ARE FICTIONAL
ANY SIMILARITY TO REALITY IS COINCIDENTAL